# Nguyễn Thành Nguyên

#### FLUTTER DEVELOPER

My short-term have a stable job, become an excellent employee, accumulate more experience, practice skills to handle the job effectively, accurately and quickly.

My long-term goal is to explore different areas of technology and work to address the area of expertise that I want to study. I want to be an expert in a particular field of mobile programming in the long term, but I know the first step is to build a solid foundation and study the basics of programming.

#### **PROFILE**





239 Hoa Binh street, Hiep Tan Ward, Tan Phu District, HCM City

#### **EDUCATION**

**CAN THO UNIVERSITY** 

INFOTMATION TECHNOLOGY

Sep 2014 - Dec 2018

## **SKILLS**

FLUTTER, WORDPRESS, REACT NATIVE

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

April 2023 - Jan 2024

## **BAP SOFTWARE CO.,LTD**

#### **MOBILE DEVELOPER**

- State-management hooks\_riverpod, bloc
- Payment mPos
- · Research and Learning.

# Jan 2021 - Mar 2023

# CNV HOLDINGS JOINT STOCK COMPANY

# **MOBILE DEVELOPER**

- Able to working with RESTFul API, Firebase, Push Notification, Provider with Flutter.
- Deeplink open app payment Momo
- Embed payment and delivery app Ahamove
- Participate in developing some projects running on App Store and Google Play.
- Teamwork and independence.
- Research and Learning.

## Dec 2018 - Dec 2020

# JASON DIGITAL MEDIA SERVICES TRADING COMPANY LIMITED

## WEB DEVELOPER AND MOBILE BASIC

- Custom add rental Point of sale for WooCommerce.
- Used to manipulate wordpress hooks.
- Used RESTful API
- Kotlin basic
- Proficient in using Git to manage source code
- Dartcore and Widget Tree
- Debug and optimize application performance

- Proficient use of Getx
- Knowledge of MVP, MVVM, Clean Architecture
- Strong understanding of React Native framework and its core principles -Proficiency in JavaScript, TypeScript, and related libraries such as Redux
- Familiarity with RESTful APIs and their integration with mobile apps
- Knowledge of Git for version control and collaboration with other developers
- Understanding of UI/UX design principles and ability to implement designs with CSS or other styling frameworks

### **PROJECTS**

Nov 2023 - Dec 2023

#### **DRIVER MATCHING**

Language: Flutter

Team size: 2

Apr 2023 - Oct 2023

# ММР

Language: Flutter

Team size: 4

DESCRIPTION

Delivery application for transport companies

#### **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

App features

- + Notify when there are new orders
- + Displays orders that the driver has run

#### **DESCRIPTION**

Application that connects people working in all fields

#### **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

App features

- + Login Google, Apple ID, Firebase
- + Integrating AI to connect people is right for employers
- + Chat
- + Cloud storage
- + Multi language

Dec 2022 - Mar 2023

## WellNess

Language: Flutter

Team size: 2

## **DESCRIPTION**

Application to diagnose diseases through answering survey questions and pre-set video exercises

#### **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

App features

- + Identify the person in front of the camera to start the exercise
- + Record video and play audio of exercises
- + Answer diagnostic questions through a prepared set of questions

Dec 2021 - Jul 2022

**POS APP** 

Language: Flutter

Team size: 3

May 2021 - Mar 2022

**LOYALTY APP** 

Language: Flutter

Team size: 3

Jan 2021 - May 2020

**CNV Parking** 

Language: Java

Team size: 2

DESCRIPTION

Loyalty management app

**TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION** 

App features

- + Developing UI by design
- + Integration shipping Ahamove
- + Push notifications when there is an order, a reservation
- + Statistical chart display
- + Scan qr to accumulate points
- + Scan qr order and booking

Appstore:

**DESCRIPTION** 

This application serves as a comprehensive answer to the needs of firms in the e-commerce, booking, spa.

**TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION** 

App features

- + Login Google, Apple ID, Firebase
- + Developing UI by design
- + Integration Payment with Momo, Vnpay
- + Releasing app on App Store and Play Store
- + Booking, Order.

Appstore:

C3%A0-

shop/id1585634817

DESCRIPTION

Application to read magnetic cards and manage vehicles entering and leaving the parking lot

**TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION** 

App features

- + Displays vehicle list
- + Vehicle card renewal
- + Listening test to choose pictures

CH play:

hl=vi&gl=US

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

**CHAT APP** 

Language: React native

Team size: 1

**DESCRIPTION** 

Basic chat application

**TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION** 

App features

+ User Authentication: Allow users to register, log in, and log out using Firebase Authentication.

+ Real-time Messaging: Realtime Database or Firebase Cloud Firestore.

- + User Profiles
- + Chat Rooms or Groups

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020

#### **ENGLISH LEARNING APP**

Language: Flutter

Team size: 3

**DESCRIPTION** 

Application to watch videos with pronunciation according to the mouth and worth the test with pictures

#### **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

App features

- + Developing UI by design
- + Video processing at client
- + Listening test to choose pictures

Mar 2020 - July 2020

## **QUAN LY VAN TAI QUOC HUY**

Language: PHP

Team size: 6

#### **DESCRIPTION**

Website managing transportation enterprises such as: driver management, assistant management, vehicle management, tractor head, trailer

## **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

Web wordpress features

- + User authentication and authorization Shipment creation and tracking
- + Carrier management
- + Route optimization
- + Inventory management
- + Reporting and analytics
- + Billing and invoicing
- + Document management
- + Communication tools (e.g. email, messaging)
- + Integration with other systems (WMS)

Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

#### **WEB AN TUONG DEP**

Language: PHP

Team size: 3

#### **DESCRIPTION**

Website to buy, sell and rent products

# **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

Web wordpress features

- + Product rental function
- + Integration shipping
- + Rental product management function

#### **INTERESTS**

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Watching movies

Nguyen, like many people, enjoys traveling and discovering new places, cultures, and ways of life. Traveling allows them to broaden their perspectives and gain a better understanding of the world around them.

Nguyen is also someone who is always eager to learn new things. Whether it's picking up a new hobby, studying a new subject, or simply trying something new, Nguyen is always looking for ways to grow and improve.